Alright, time for another exercise.
Tudo bem, hora de outro exerccio.
So, back in the Mocking folder, look at this class.
Ento, de volta  pasta Mocking, veja essa classe.
InstallerHelper. This is the
InstallerHelper. Este  o cdigo que um
code that one of my students sent me. So if you are that person who sent me this
dos meus alunos me enviou. Ento, se voc  aquela pessoa que me
code, thank you very much for sharing your code, we're going to use this as an example of a
enviou este cdigo, muito obrigado por compartilhar seu cdigo, vamos usar isso como um exemplo de
code that touches an external resource. So here we have this method,
um cdigo que toca um recurso externo. Ento, aqui temos esse
DownloadInstaller. It takes a customer name, and
mtodo, o DownloadInstaller.  necessrio um nome de
InstallerName, and uses the WebClient class,
cliente e nome de instalador e usa a classe WebClient
to download the file from the internet. The first
para baixar o arquivo da Internet. O primeiro argumento para
argument to this method is the location, or the URL of this
esse mtodo  o local ou a URL
file. So here we're using string.format to construct a URL
desse arquivo. Ento aqui estamos usando string. formato para construir um
like this. example.com. The first argument after that
URL como este. exemplo. com. O primeiro
is customerName, and the second is installerName.
argumento depois disso  customerName e o segundo  installerName.
And this is the second argument to this download file
E este  o segundo argumento para este mtodo
method. And this argument specifies the location on the
de arquivo de download. E esse argumento especifica o local no sistema
file system where we need to store this file. As you can see,
de arquivos em que precisamos armazenar esse arquivo. Como voc pode ver,
the call to download file is wrapped inside
a chamada para baixar o arquivo est dentro
a try cash block, so if everything goes well, you're going to
de um bloco try cash, ento se tudo
return true, otherwise we're going to return false.
correr bem, voc retornar true, caso contrrio, retornaremos false.
So, now, I want you to use what you have learned in this section, and write
Ento, agora, quero que voc use o que aprendeu nesta seo e escreva um
a required unit test for this class. Next, we're going to look at my
teste de unidade necessrio para essa classe. Em seguida, vamos
solution.
ver minha soluo.